export const data = [
    {front: 'か', back: 'KA'}, 
    {front: 'あ', back: 'A'}, 
    {front: 'さ', back: 'SA'}, 
    {front: 'た', back: 'TA'}, 
  ];

    export const cards = [
    {front: 'か', back: 'KA', id: 1, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'あ', back: 'A', id: 2, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'さ', back: 'SA', id: 3, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'た', back: 'TA', id: 4, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'な', back: 'NA', id: 5, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'は', back: 'HA', id: 6, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'ま', back: 'MA', id: 7, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'や', back: 'YA', id: 8, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'か', back: 'KA', id: 9, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'ら', back: 'RA', id: 10, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'わ', back: 'WA', id: 11, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'い', back: 'I', id: 12, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'き', back: 'KI', id: 13, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'し', back: 'SHI', id: 14, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'ち', back: 'CHI', id: 15, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'に', back: 'NI', id: 16, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'ひ', back: 'HI', id: 17, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'み', back: 'MI', id: 18, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'り', back: 'RI', id: 19, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'う', back: 'U', id: 20, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'く', back: 'KU', id: 21, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'す', back: 'SU', id: 22, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'つ', back: 'TSU', id: 23, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'ぬ', back: 'NU', id: 24, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'ふ', back: 'FU', id: 25, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'む', back: 'MU', id: 26, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'ゆ', back: 'YU', id: 27, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'る', back: 'RU', id: 28, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'え', back: 'E', id: 29, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'け', back: 'KE', id: 30, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'せ', back: 'SE', id: 31, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'て', back: 'TE', id: 32, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'ね', back: 'NE', id: 33, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'へ', back: 'HE', id: 34, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'め', back: 'ME', id: 35, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'れ', back: 'RE', id: 36, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'お', back: 'O', id: 37, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'こ', back: 'KO', id: 38, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'そ', back: 'SO', id: 39, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'と', back: 'TO', id: 40, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'の', back: 'NO', id: 41, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'ほ', back: 'HO', id: 42, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'も', back: 'MO', id: 43, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'よ', back: 'YO', id: 44, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ろ', back: 'RO', id: 45, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'を', back: 'WO', id: 46, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']}, 
    {front: 'ん', back: 'N', id: 47, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'カ', back: 'KA', id: 48, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'サ', back: 'SA', id: 49, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'タ', back: 'TA', id: 50, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ナ', back: 'NA', id: 51, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ハ', back: 'HA', id: 52, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'マ', back: 'MA', id: 53, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ヤ', back: 'YA', id: 54, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ラ', back: 'RA', id: 55, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ワ', back: 'WA', id: 56, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'キ', back: 'KI', id: 57, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'シ', back: 'SHI', id: 58, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'チ', back: 'CHI', id: 59, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ニ', back: 'NI', id: 60, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ヒ', back: 'HI', id: 61, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ミ', back: 'MI', id: 62, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'リ', back: 'RI', id: 63, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ク', back: 'KU', id: 64, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ス', back: 'SU', id: 65, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ツ', back: 'TSU', id: 66, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ヌ', back: 'NU', id: 67, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'フ', back: 'FU', id: 68, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ム', back: 'MU', id: 69, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ユ', back: 'YU', id: 70, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ル', back: 'RU', id: 71, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ケ', back: 'KE', id: 72, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'セ', back: 'SE', id: 73, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'テ', back: 'TE', id: 74, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ネ', back: 'NE', id: 75, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ヘ', back: 'HE', id: 76, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'メ', back: 'ME', id: 77, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'レ', back: 'RE', id: 78, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'コ', back: 'KO', id: 79, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ソ', back: 'SO', id: 80, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ト', back: 'TO', id: 81, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ノ', back: 'NO', id: 82, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ホ', back: 'HO', id: 83, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'モ', back: 'MO', id: 84, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ヨ', back: 'YO', id: 85, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ロ', back: 'RO', id: 86, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ヲ', back: 'WO', id: 87, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ン', back: 'N', id: 88, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ア', back: 'A', id: 89, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'イ', back: 'I', id: 90, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'ウ', back: 'U', id: 91, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'エ', back: 'E', id: 92, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'オ', back: 'O', id: 93, difficulty: 1, tags:['katakana', 'gojūon']},
    {front: 'が', back: 'GA', id: 94, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']},
    {front: 'ざ', back: 'ZA', id: 95, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']},
    {front: 'だ', back: 'DA', id: 96, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']},
    {front: 'ば', back: 'BA', id: 97, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']},
    {front: 'ぱ', back: 'PA', id: 98, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']},
    {front: 'ぎ', back: 'GI', id: 99, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']},
    {front: 'じ', back: 'JI', id: 100, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']},
    {front: 'ぢ', back: 'DI', id: 101, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']},
    {front: 'び', back: 'BI', id: 102, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']},
    {front: 'ぴ', back: 'PI', id: 103, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']},
    {front: 'ぐ', back: 'GU', id: 104, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']},
    {front: 'ず', back: 'ZU', id: 105, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']},
    {front: 'づ', back: 'DU', id: 106, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']},
    {front: 'ぶ', back: 'BU', id: 107, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']},
    {front: 'ぷ', back: 'PU', id: 108, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']},
    {front: 'げ', back: 'GE', id: 109, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']},
    {front: 'ぜ', back: 'ZE', id: 110, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']},
    {front: 'で', back: 'DE', id: 111, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']},
    {front: 'べ', back: 'BE', id: 112, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']},
    {front: 'ぺ', back: 'PE', id: 113, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']},
    {front: 'ご', back: 'GO', id: 114, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']},
    {front: 'ぞ', back: 'ZO', id: 115, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']},
    {front: 'ど', back: 'DO', id: 116, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']},
    {front: 'ぼ', back: 'BO', id: 117, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']},
    {front: 'ぽ', back: 'PO', id: 118, difficulty: 1, tags:['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']},
  ];

  export const difficulties = [
    {index: 1, name: 'easy', color: '#E8E8E8', textColor: '#686868'},
    {index: 2, name: 'normal', color: '#C0C0C0', textColor: 'white'},
    {index: 3, name: 'hard', color: '#989898', textColor: 'white'},
    {index: 4, name: 'impossible', color: '#686868', textColor: 'white'}];

  export const collection1 = {
      id: 1,
      type: 'collection',
      cards: [1,2,3],
  };

  export const exercise1 = {
    type: 'exercise',
    id: 1,
    name: 'Katakanas',
    urlName: 'katakanas',
    tag: 'katakana',
    // cards: [48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59, 60, 61, 62, 63, 64, 65, 66, 67, 68, 69, 70, 71, 72, 73, 74, 75, 76, 77, 78, 79, 80, 81, 82, 83, 84, 85, 86, 87, 88, 89, 90, 91, 92, 93],
  };

  export const exercise2 = {
    type: 'exercise',
    id: 2,
    name: 'Hiraganas',
    urlName: 'hiraganas',
    tag: 'hiragana',
    // cards: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47],
  };